<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LeMaterial</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on LeMaterial</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2020-2024 Entalpic</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 17:19:07 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The mission</title><link>/docs/about/the-mission/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/the-mission/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>LeMaterial&lt;/strong> is an open-science initiative dedicated to advancing materials research by providing harmonized data, useful tools, ML models, and various other collaborative resources. Our mission is to drive progress at the intersection of materials science and machine learning (ML), opening new opportunities to uncover novel materials and explore chemical spaces with unprecedented depth.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>/docs/about/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/datasets/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of LeMaterial, we released and will maintain different datasets, unifying and standardizing data from existing databases:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;code>LeMat-Bulk&lt;/code>: released in December 2024, it unifies data from Materials Project, Alexandria, and OQMD into a high-quality resource with consistent and systematic properties (6,7M entries, 7 material properties)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Citations</title><link>/docs/about/citations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/citations/</guid><description>&lt;p>By downloading content from LeMaterial, you agree to accept the Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 license implying that Content may be copied, distributed, transmitted, and adapted, without obtaining specific permission from LeMaterial, provided proper attribution is given to LeMaterial. If you use the LeMaterial as a resource in your research, please cite the &lt;a href="https://huggingface.co/datasets/LeMaterial/LeMat-Bulk#citation-information">citation section&lt;/a> from our data-card (paper to come). &lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/">CC-BY-4.0&lt;/a> requires proper acknowledgement.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to join?</title><link>/docs/about/how-to-join/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/how-to-join/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are excited to invite AI practitioners from diverse backgrounds to join LeMaterial! Note that LeMaterial is a research collaboration and is open to participants who have&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>/docs/about/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="our-pledge">Our Pledge&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our
community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body
size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender
identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status,
nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual
identity and orientation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 17:19:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>