<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on LeMaterial</title><link>/docs/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on LeMaterial</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2020-2024 Entalpic</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The mission</title><link>/docs/about/the-mission/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/the-mission/</guid><description>&lt;p>LeMaterial is an open-science initiative at the intersection of materials science and machine learning, created to accelerate the discovery of novel materials and deepen our understanding of the chemical space.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Datasets</title><link>/docs/about/datasets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/datasets/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of LeMaterial, we released and will maintain different datasets, unifying and standardizing data from existing databases:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>LeMat-Bulk&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Released in December 2024&lt;/li>
&lt;li>This dataset unifies data from Materials Project, Alexandria, and OQMD into a high-quality resource with consistent and systematic properties (6,7M entries, 7 material properties)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://huggingface.co/datasets/LeMaterial/LeMat-Bulk">https://huggingface.co/datasets/LeMaterial/LeMat-Bulk&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>LeMat-BulkUnique&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Citations</title><link>/docs/about/citations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/citations/</guid><description>&lt;p>All content released under the LeMaterial initiative is distributed under the Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International (CC BY 4.0) license. This means the datasets and tools may be freely copied, distributed, modified, and used for derivative works, provided that appropriate credit is given to the LeMaterial project.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to join?</title><link>/docs/about/how-to-join/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/how-to-join/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>LeMaterial is an open and collaborative initiative&lt;/strong> — and anyone with an interest in materials science, machine learning, or open scientific infrastructure is welcome to join. Whether you’re a student, researcher, engineer, or just curious, there’s a place for you in the community.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>/docs/about/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/about/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="our-pledge">Our Pledge&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our
community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body
size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender
identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status,
nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual
identity and orientation.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>